{
  "geoquestions": [
     {
      "id" : 1,
      "questionType" : "true_false",
      "questionText" : "Paris is in Italy.",
      "correctAnswer" : "false",
      "options" : ["true", "false"]
      },
     {
      "id": 2,
      "questionType" : "text_input",
      "questionText" : "Is London located in England or Germany?",
      "correctAnswer" : "England",
      "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
      },
     {
      "id" : 3,
      "questionType" : "true_false",
      "questionText" : "Which continent is China in?",
      "correctAnswer" : "Asia",
      "options" : ["Europe", "Asia"]
      },
     {
      "id" : 4,
      "questionType" : "true_false",
      "questionText" : "Is Asia a country?",
      "correctAnswer" : "no",
      "options" : ["yes", "no"]
      },
     {
      "id" : 5,
      "questionType" : "true_false",
      "questionText" : "True or false: Russia touches 2 continents.",
      "correctAnswer" : "true",
      "options" : ["true", "false"]
      },
      {
      "id" : 6,
      "questionType" : "text_input",
      "questionText" : "What continent is Morocco located in?",
      "correctAnswer" : "Africa",
      "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
      },
      {
      "id" : 7,
      "questionType" : "true_false",
      "questionText" : "What is the closest ocean to Madagascar?",
      "correctAnswer" : "Indian Ocean",
      "options" : ["Indian Ocean", "Pacific Ocean"]
      },
      {
      "id" : 8,
      "questionType" : "text_input",
      "questionText" : "What country is the Nile located in?",
      "correctAnswer" : "Egypt",
      "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
      },
      {
      "id" : 9,
      "questionType" : "true_false",
      "questionText" : "Which continent is known for big spiders?",
      "correctAnswer" : "Australia",
      "options" : ["Europe", "Australia"]
      },
      {
      "id" : 10,
      "questionType" : "true_false",
      "questionText" : "Australia has kangaroos.",
      "correctAnswer" : "true",
      "options" : ["true", "false"]
      },
      {
      "id" : 11,
      "questionType" : "text_input",
      "questionText" : "Fill in the blank: Jamaica is located in the ________ Sea.",
      "correctAnswer" : "Caribbean",
      "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
      },
      {
      "id" : 12,
      "questionType" : "text_input",
      "questionText" : "What City is known as The Big Apple?",
      "correctAnswer" : "New York",
      "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
      },
      {
      "id" : 13,
      "questionType" : "text_input",
      "questionText" : "Fill in the blank: Uruguay touches the _______ Ocean.",
      "correctAnswer" : "Atlantic",
      "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
      },
      {
      "id" : 14,
      "questionType" : "true_false",
      "questionText" : "Where is the city Perth located?",
      "correctAnswer" : "Australia",
      "options" : ["Thailand", "Australia"]
      },
      {
      "id" : 15,
      "questionType" : "true_false",
      "questionText" : "What country shares an island with the Dominican Republic?",
      "correctAnswer" : "Haiti",
      "options" : ["Guadeloupe", "Haiti"]
      },
      {
      "id" : 16,
      "questionType" : "text_input",
      "questionText" : "What state is Houston located in?",
      "correctAnswer" : "answer_to_question"
      
      },
      {
      "id" : 17,
      "questionType" : "text_input",
      "questionText" : "Fill in the blank: Mexico is next to the _____ Ocean.",
      "correctAnswer" : "answer_to_question"
      
      },
      {
      "id" : 18,
      "questionType" : "true_false",
      "questionText" : "Toronto is located in ______.",
      "correctAnswer" : "Canada",
      "options" : ["Canada", "the United States"]
      },
      {
      "id" : 19,
      "questionType" : "true_false",
      "questionText" : "What country is Alaska part of?",
      "correctAnswer" : "The United States",
      "options" : ["Canada", "The United States"]
      },
      {
      "id" : 20,
      "questionType" : "true_false",
      "questionText" : "Which island is NOT part of the Caribbean?",
      "correctAnswer" : "Cyprus",
      "options" : ["Martinique", "Cyprus"]
      }
  ],
  "mathquestions": [
                     {
                      "id" : 1,
                      "questionType" : "true_false",
                      "questionText" : "2 + 2 = 4",
                      "correctAnswer" : "true"
                      },
                     {
                      "id" : 2,
                      "questionType" : "text_input",
                      "questionText" : "What is the value of the expression 1+1",
                      "correctAnswer" : "2",
                      "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
                      },
                     {
                      "id" : 3,
                      "questionType" : "true_false",
                      "questionText" : "Is 18 even or odd?",
                      "correctAnswer" : "even",
                      "options" : ["even", "odd"]
                      },
                     {
                      "id" : 4,
                      "questionType" : "true_false",
                      "questionText" : "The square root of 36 is 4.",
                      "correctAnswer" : "false",
                      "options" : ["true", "false"]
                      },
                     {
                      "id" : 5,
                      "questionType" : "text_input",
                      "questionText" : "9^2 = ___",
                      "correctAnswer" : "81",
                      "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
                      },
                      {
                      "id" : 6,
                      "questionType" : "text_input",
                      "questionText" : "32 + 64 = ___",
                      "correctAnswer" : "96",
                      "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
                      },
                      {
                      "id" : 7,
                      "questionType" : "true_false",
                      "questionText" : "5 x 5 = ___",
                      "correctAnswer" : "25",
                      "options" : ["52", "25"]
                      },
                      {
                      "id" : 8,
                      "questionType" : "true_false",
                      "questionText" : "32 - 17 = ___",
                      "correctAnswer" : "15",
                      "options" : ["19", "15"]
                      },
                      {
                      "id" : 9,
                      "questionType" : "true_false",
                      "questionText" : "103 + 207 = ___",
                      "correctAnswer" : "310",
                      "options" : ["310", "291"]
                      },
                      {
                      "id" : 10,
                      "questionType" : "true_false",
                      "questionText" : "What quadrant is (-5, 3) located in on a graph?",
                      "correctAnswer" : "Quadrant 2",
                      "options" : ["Quadrant 2", "Quadrant 4"]
                      },
                      {
                      "id" : 11,
                      "questionType" : "true_false",
                      "questionText" : "70 x 3 = ___",
                      "correctAnswer" : "210",
                      "options" : ["180", "210"]
                      },
                      {
                      "id" : 12,
                      "questionType" : "true_false",
                      "questionText" : "200 - 156 = ",
                      "correctAnswer" : "44",
                      "options" : ["52", "44"]
                      
                      },
                      {
                      "id" : 13,
                      "questionType" : "text_input",
                      "questionText" : "Find f(3) if f(x)= 2^x + 7",
                      "correctAnswer" : "15",
                      "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
                      },
                      {
                      "id" : 14,
                      "questionType" : "true_false",
                      "questionText" : "Is there a square root of 2?",
                      "correctAnswer" : "No",
                      "options" : ["Yes", "No"]
                      },
                      {
                      "id" : 15,
                      "questionType" : "true_false",
                      "questionText" : "True or false: Quadrant 3 on a graph only contains negatve numbers.",
                      "correctAnswer" : "True",
                      "options" : ["True", "False"]
                      },
                      {
                      "id" : 16,
                      "questionType" : "text_input",
                      "questionText" : "The E in PEMDAS stands for ________.",
                      "correctAnswer" : "exponent",
                      "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
                      },
                      {
                      "id" : 17,
                      "questionType" : "text_input",
                      "questionText" : "21 - 23 = ___",
                      "correctAnswer" : "-2",
                      "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
                      },
                      {
                      "id" : 18,
                      "questionType" : "true_false",
                      "questionText" : "A quadrilateral is a shape with ___ sides.",
                      "correctAnswer" : "4",
                      "options" : ["6", "4"]
                      },
                      {
                      "id" : 19,
                      "questionType" : "text_input",
                      "questionText" : "Find x if 5x + 3 = 13",
                      "correctAnswer" : "2",
                      "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
                      },
                      {
                      "id" : 20,
                      "questionType" : "text_input",
                      "questionText" : "What is 21 / 3 ?",
                      "correctAnswer" : "7",
                      "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
                      }

  ]
}